{"data":[{"question":"There is ______ water in this glass!","a":"so many","b":"so","c":"so much","d":"as","answer":"3","explain":"\n- \"So\" can be combined with \"much\" or \"little\" plus a non-countable noun to show extremes in amount. This form is often used in exclamations","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"12","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"Will you ______ us a story, Mum?","a":"tell","b":"say","c":"told","d":"said","answer":"1","explain":"- You say something\n\n- You tell someone something","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"12","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"What are you going to ______ at the meeting tonight?","a":"tell","b":"say","c":"told","d":"said","answer":"2","explain":"\n- You say something \n- You tell someone something \n- Be going to Verb","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"12","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"There are ______ trees in this park!","a":"so many","b":"so","c":"so much","d":"as","answer":"1","explain":"\n- \"So\" can be combined with \"much\" or \"little\" plus a non-countable noun to show extremes in amount. This form is often used in exclamations. ","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"12","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"I didn't know these houses were _______ big.","a":"so much","b":"so many","c":"so","d":"as","answer":"3","explain":"\n- So \/ Such in exclamations: \n+ Such + noun (singular\/plural) \n+ So + adjective ","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"12","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"Mum, ______ me a story!","a":"tell","b":"say","c":"told","d":"said","answer":"1","explain":"\n- You say something \n- You tell someone something ","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"12","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"They ______ that it was too late.","a":"say","b":"told","c":"said","d":"tell","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Say that + clause","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"12","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"What did Mr Smith ______ your mother?","a":"tell","b":"say","c":"told","d":"said","answer":"1","explain":"- You say something\n\n- You tell someone something","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"12","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"He ______ that he'll arrive in the morning.","a":"tell","b":"say","c":"told","d":"said","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Say + that + clause \n- Past simple tense: say- said","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"12","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"Did your teacher _______ you lhat?","a":"tell","b":"say","c":"told","d":"said","answer":"1","explain":"\n- You say something \n- You tell someone something \n- Did + S + V-infinitive + O? ","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"12","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"}]}